<resources>

    <!-- Main String Information -->
    <string name="app_name">Scavenger</string>
    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_likes">Likes</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password</string>

    <!-- Sign In / Sign Up String Information -->
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="full_name_text_view">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="terms_signin">By Signing In, you agree to Scavenger\'s Terms &amp; Conditions and Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="terms_signup">By Signing Up, you agree to Scavenger\'s Terms &amp; Conditions and Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_facebook">Sign In with Facebook</string>
    <string name="sign_up_with_facebook">Sign Up with Facebook</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign In with Google</string>
    <string name="sign_up_with_google">Sign Up with Google</string>
    <string name="signin_or">OR</string>
    <string name="forgot_your_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="no_account_signup">Don\'t have an account? Sign Up!</string>
    <string name="signup_header_description">Sign Up to Save Recipes so you can go back to them later!</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_hint">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="passwords_do_not_match">*Passwords do not match</string>

    <!-- Search Fragment String Information -->
    <string name="startup_message_1">Scavenge For Recipes!</string>
    <string name="startup_message_2">Find Recipes You\'ll Love!</string>
    <string name="startup_message_3">Add Up All The\nThyme You Can Save!</string>
    <string name="startup_message_4">Break An Egg, Make An Omelet!</string>
    <string name="startup_message_5">Check The Way Back Of The Cabinet!</string>
    <string name="no_recipes_found">UH OH… Seems like nothing was found.</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No Internet connection.</string>

    <!-- Like String Information -->
    <string name="not_signed_in">You are not Signed In. Sign In or Sign Up to save and view your Likes.</string>
    <string name="no_likes">You don\'t have any Likes. Go out there and discover something great!</string>
    <string name="likes_not_connected">You are not connected to the Internet. Your Likes will be loaded when you reconnect.</string>

    <!-- Recipe Card String Information -->
    <string name="recipe_image_content_descr">Recipe Image</string>
    <string name="more_button_content_descr">More</string>
    <string name="recipe_like_button_content_descr">Recipe Like</string>
    <string name="servings_text">Serves %1$d</string>
    <string name="calories">Calories</string>
    <string name="carbs">Carbs</string>
    <string name="fat">Fat</string>
    <string name="protein">Protein</string>
    <string name="ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="nutrition_facts">Nutrition Facts</string>
    <string name="view_recipe">View Recipe</string>
    <string name="edamam_branding">Edamam Branding</string>

    <!-- Forgot Password Information -->
    <string name="password_instructions_text">Please enter your email address. Reset instructions will be sent to you.</string>
    <string name="send_email_button">Send Email</string>

    <!-- Feedback String Information -->
    <string name="report_problem_text">Please only leave feedback about Scavenger and our features. If you would like to report a specific recipe for issues regarding profanity, nudity, or language, please use the report feature on the recipe\'s card. All reports are subject to our Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="feedback_text">Please only leave feedback about Scavenger and our features. If you would like to report a specific recipe for issues regarding profanity, nudity, or language, please use the report feature on the recipe\'s card. All reports are subject to our Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="report_problem_edittext">What went wrong?</string>
    <string name="report_a_problem">Report a Problem</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="feedback_edittext">What would you like us to improve?</string>

    <!-- ID String Information -->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">505719136936823</string>
    <string name="clientId_web_googleSignIn">565312817175-cipp792csradj5qukdb836j8e9tuq7gr.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <!-- Miscellaneous String Information -->
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="search_menu_copy">Copy Recipe URL</string>
    <string name="search_menu_share">Share Recipe</string>
    <string name="search_menu_report">Report…</string>
    <string name="retry_connection">Retry Connection</string>
    <string name="match_ingredients_on_search">This can occur if Match Ingredients is On</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="help_center">Help Center</string>

    <!-- Open Source Library String Information -->
    <string name="open_source_libraries">Open Source Libraries</string>
    <string name="libraries_we_use">Libraries We Use</string>
    <string name="osl_header_detail">The following sets forth attribution notices for third part software that may be contained in portions of the Scavenger product. We thank the open source community for all of their contributions.</string>
    <string name="picasso_license_info"><b>Picasso</b>
        \nCopyright © 2013 Square, Inc.
        \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); You may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
        \n\n<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a>
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="google_att">License for everything not indicated as Third Party and not otherwise marked:\n\nGoogle License\nCopyright © 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\nThe views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed or implied, of Google, Inc.</string>
    <string name="apache_license"><b>Apache License</b>
        \nCopyright © 2020 Michael Hamm
        \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\"); You may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
        \n\n<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a>
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="leakcanary_license"><b>Leak Canary</b>
        \nCopyright © 2015 Square, Inc.
        \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); You may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
        \n\n<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a>
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="shimmer_license"><b>Shimmer for Android</b>
        \nBSD License
        \n\nFor shimmer-android software
        \n\nCopyright © Facebook, Inc. and its affiliates. All rights reserved.
        \n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
        \n\n- Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
        \n\n- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
        \n\n- Neither the name Facebook nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
        \n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
    <string name="retrofit_license"><b>Retrofit</b>
        \nCopyright © 2013 Square, Inc.
        \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); You may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at

        \n\n<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a>
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <!--<string name="rxjava_license"><b>RxJava</b>
        \nCopyright © 2016-present, RxJava Contributors.
        \n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); You may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
        \n\n<a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</a>
        \n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>-->
    <string name="main_search_background">Main Search Background</string>
    <string name="grocery_list_text1">In order to create and save your grocery list, you must Sign In or Sign Up. By Signing Up for Scavenger, you get access to not only saving your most liked recipes but you can also...</string>
    <string name="grocery_list_text2">- Add ingredients from any recipe</string>
    <string name="grocery_list_text3">- Sync your grocery list across all of your devices</string>
    <string name="grocery_list_text4">The best part is that Signing Up is Free!</string>
    <string name="close_list">close list</string>
    <string name="grocery_list">Grocery List</string>
    <string name="search_recyclerview_content_descr">Search List View</string>
    <string name="likes_recyclerview_content_descr">Likes List View</string>
    <string name="nutrition_card_information">Nutrition Information</string>
    <string name="password_for_sign_in">Password for Sign in</string>
    <string name="add_item_button">add item</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recipe_item_screen">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="recipe_instructions">Instructions</string>


</resources>
